剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
我不在乎Jack怎么说
I don't care what Jack said.
我们要把他救回来
They've got him. We have to get him back.
我欠他的
I owe him that.
那个屋子里的男人 你以前见过他?
The man in the house. You said you seen him before?
就是珍珠舱录像里的那个人
On the video feed from the pearl station.
我们为什么还要兜圈子呢
Why are we continuing to play this little game,
为什么不直接切入正题?
when we all know it has moved to the next stage?
这张地图显示所有电能
This is a map showing electrical and data cabling
提供给了一个住宅区
comprised of houses and dormitories.
那地方一定很值得拜访
Sounds like a place well worth visiting.
当我看见闪电击打顶棚时你被电死了
I saw a lightning hit the roof. You were electrocuted.
你下水去救Claire的时候
And when you heard Claire was in the water,
你自己却淹死了
you drown trying to save her.
结果我下了水 你就得救了 我试过了 兄弟
I dove in myself so you never went in. I'm trying pal,
我救了你两次 但不论我怎么做
I tried twice to save you, but no matter what I try to do...
你都会死的 Charlie
you gonna die Charlie.
妈妈? 妈妈!
Mom!
看啊 Aron 你妈妈终于决定起床了
Oh look, Aaron! Your mom has finaly decided to wake up.
多亏了我借走你的小矮人 你才睡着的
The only way I could get you to sleep in was to borrow the midget.
这些都是什么?
And, what is all this?
开味酒和这岛上神秘的水果
An aperitive, of mysterious island fruit.
然后还有我特意为你准备的野餐
Before the breakfast picnic I have set up in your honor
就在不远的沙滩
a short walk down the beach.
你怎么了Charlie?
What's gotten into you, Charlie?
一个星期以来你都很沮丧
It's just, you've been so depressed all week,
而现在 野餐和枕边小吃?
and now it's breakfast in bed and picnics?
早晨醒来我想
I woke up this morning, and I thought,
是时候振作精神了 让自己占有这一天
it's time to stop feeling sorry for yourself and seize the day,
然后我就想到了你
and I can't think of anyone I'd rather do some day-seizing with than you.
那...你怎么说?
So... What do you say?
让我们把这小天使
Let's drop the cherub off
交给Sun阿姨和Jin叔叔
with auntie Sun and uncle Jin,
让我们去享受吧
and you and I go for a little stroll.
正合我意
I would love to.
照小溪的方位 我们应该在这里
From the position of this stream, we should be here,
如果比例正确的话
and if the scale is right,
他的人一定在那个方向的两英里外
his people are 2 miles in that direction.
我没有期望你的确认
I don't expect you to confirm that.
这只是电缆的地图 Sayid
It's an electrical wiring map, Sayid.
我不像你那么确定它的精确度
I'm not sure it's as accurate as you think.
那当然没有你那神奇的棍子来的精确
Well, it's certainly not as infallible as the magical carvings on your stick.
那棍子带我们去了那个站
Hey, the stick didget us to that station.
是那个你不小心炸掉的站吗?
Oh, the station which you accidentally blew up.
如果你提醒我那到处是C-4的话
If you'd have warned me that the basement was rigged with C-4,
我也许会小心点
I might've been a little more careful.
你就不能告诉我们正确的方向吗?
Why don't you just tell us if we're going the right way?
你们走的没错
You're going the right way.
我们为什么让他活着呢?
Remind me why we're keeping him alive.
你有什么建议 像打狗一样杀了他?
What do you suggest, we shoot him like a dog?
不 我喜欢狗
No. I like dogs.
他是对的 他们不会用他的生命和你的朋友交换的
He's right. They would not trade his life for your friend's.
我们应该杀了他
We should shoot him.
够了 谁都别说了
Enough! Nobody's shooting anybody.
地图告诉我们他们的方位他说我们的方向是正确的
The map says where they are, and he says the map is right,
所以继续前进吧
so just keep moving.
我们到了
Okay, here we are, here we are.
不错是吧?
Not bad, eh?
简直棒极了
Not bad at all.
你先请坐吧
Well, if you'll take your seat,
我们有麦片 新鲜的水果沙拉
we will begin with our first course,which is cereal.We have fresh fruit salad
早上好
Good morning.
恩...早上好
Good morning yourself.
什么风把你吹来了 Desmond?
What brings you down to the beach?
最近有许多野猪出没
Boar are running thick.
我希望你和我一起去打猎
I was hoping you might want to join me on a hunt.
谢谢你的邀请
Thanks for the invite,
但我们正在准备野餐
but as you can see, we're just about to begin a picnic.
我认为打猎是一种...
Well, I think hunting might be a...
很好的方式来消磨你的一天 Charlie
a better way to spend your day, Charlie.
我的意思是所有的事中
I mean, of all the things you could choose to do today,
打猎无疑是最佳选择
hunting with me might be your best option.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
怎么了?
What is it?
我知道怎么离开这座岛了
I think I know how to get us off this island.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧翻译组制作
YYeTs制作之美剧字幕首发网站 www.YYETS.com
翻译: 许愿   校对: 许愿
后期: 梁良   双语字幕: 七色九天
Sun! Jin!
Claire 你怎么了?
Claire, what's the matter?
我需要Jin的网和鱼
I need Jin's nets and fish.
我们要快点...还有水桶 我需要那个
We've gotta hurry. And buckets...I'm gonna need those, too.
我们必须抓一只鸟
We have to catch the birds.
他们刚飞过 而且就在这停留一天
They just flew over, and they're only gonna be here today,
所以要捉的话 只有今天
so to catch one, we need to do it now.
那听起来很有趣
Oh, this sounds like fun.
你能弄些网来吗?
Can you get some nets?
网用来干嘛Barb...
Nets for what, Barb...
网用来干嘛 Claire?
Nets for what, Claire?
5分钟前 一群海鸟飞过我的头顶
Okay, five minutes ago, a flock of sea birds flew over my head.
海鸟会迁移
Seabirds are migratory,
他们会继续向南飞
which means they're gonna keep heading south.
抱歉 我还是不明白
I'm sorry. I don't understand why we need to...
他们被挂了标签
They're tagged.
标签?
Tagged?
科学家给他们做了标签 为了追踪研究他们
Scientists tag these birds so they can track them.
如果他们到了澳大利亚或新西兰
So when they eventually land in Australia or New Zealand or wherever,
有人会收集他们的
somebody's gonna gather them up.
如果我们捉住一只
We can send a message.
我们可以靠他们传递消息
If we can catch one.
好了 这是我们的计划
Okay, so here's the plan.
首先把鱼弄碎
First, we've gotta cut up these fish, make chum.
鸟儿会来觅食的
That'll get the birds to settle in the water.
我们要重新布置网
And then, um, we're gonna need to cut up some of this net.
Charlie能把刀递给我吗?
Charlie, can you go get some knives?
Charlie
Charlie!
是的
Yeah.
你是怎么知道这些的 Claire?
How do you even know this stuff about birds?
那是因为我和妈妈看太多自然节目了
I watched a lot of nature shows with my mum.
那也不能让你成为专家啊
Doesn't exactly make you an expert.
我只是...
I just...
我只是不想让你浪费时间罢了
I don't want to see you wasting your time, that's all.
你不是说好"占有"这一天的吗?
So what happened to seizing the day?
抱歉
Sorry.
是我没发现这一点
Don't see the point.
稳住了 亲爱的
Hold still, dear.
马上就好
Just another second.
行了
There.
没事了
We're through now.
Littleton女士 我是Barnes警官
Ms. Littleton, I'm Officer Barnes.
很抱歉打扰您 但我需要问几个问题
Sorry to bother you, but I need to ask you a few questions.
事故是怎么发生的?
Can I ask you how the accident happened?
一辆卡车把我们撞出路面
A truck forced us off the road.
谁在驾驶?
Okay, and who was driving?
我
Me.
有人联系你父亲吗?
Has anyone contacted your father?
我2岁时父亲就去世了
My father died when I was 2.
很抱歉
Sorry to hear that.
我和卡车司机谈过
I spoke with the truck driver.
他很好
He's fine, by the way.
他说你撞了他...
He said that when you hit him...
不 是他撞的我们
No, he hit us.
事故发生时你的车速是多少?
About what speed would you say that happened when you were driving?
他突然就冒了出来 我没有...
It just came out of nowhere.
你没有回答我的问题 Littleton女士
That's not the question I asked, Ms. Littleton.
我不知道当时的车速
I don't know how fast I was driving.
你为什么要问这些问题?
Why are you even asking me these questions?
抱歉这是程序
These questions are standard procedure when there's a fatality.
我母亲在开刀
My mother is in surgery.
她还没死
She's not dead.
是啊
Right.
那就是了
So she is.
这不是我的错
You know, this is not my fault!
我没有说是你的错
Didn't say it was.
祝你有愉快的一天 Littleton女士
Good day, Ms. Littleton.
能问你个问题吗?
Can I ask you something?
我告诉你你女儿和他们在一起...
I told you that your daughter was living with them...
而你竟然没问我一个问题
and you haven't asked me a single question about her.
你没有...
You haven't...
你的朋友 Jack
Your friend Jack,
你关切他吗?
you care about him?
是的
Yes.
设想一下16年后
Imagine 16 years from now,
你被告知他还活着
you're told he's still alive.
然而你告诉自己
But in your heart,
他可能甚至都不记得你了
you know that he wouldn't remember you.
他根本不认识你了
He wouldn't know you.
那还会了解
Wouldn't even know
你关切过他吗?
that you ever cared about him.
我没有问你我女儿的事...
I haven't asked you questions about my daughter...
因为我不想知道答案
because I do not want to know the answers.
水?
Water?
不了 谢谢
No, thank you.
你是怎么来这里的?
So how'd you get here?
怎么来到这座岛上的?
How'd you get onto this island?
不要浪费口舌了 他说的都不是真话
Don't waste your breath. Whatever he says will be a lie.
24岁是我被招入了新兵
I was recruited when I was 24.
有一个人和我接触...
I was approached by a man...
我没有问什么时候 我问你是怎么来的
I didn't ask you when I asked you how.
坐潜水艇来的
They brought me on the submarine.
你们的人...他们能随意进出?
So your people, they can just come and go whenever they want?
去 是的 可两星期以前
Go, yes, but two weeks ago,
海底灯标停止接收信号
our underwater beacon stopped emitting its locator signal.
出了事故...是电磁回路
There was an event...an electromagnetic pulse.
回来就不可能了
It would be impossible to come back.
你为什么想回来?
Why would you want to come back?
你不会明白的
You would not understand.
说来听听
Try me.
我不会说的
I misspoke.
我想说的是
What I meant to say is,
你没有理解的能力
you're not capable of understanding.
那又是为什么呢?
And why am I not capable?
Kate
因为你不在名单上
Because you are not on the list.
什么名单?
What list?
那个把我带来这里的人
The man who brought me here,
和所有来这里的人
who brought all of my people here,
他是一个...伟大的人
he is... a magnificent man.
如果Ben很伟大 那为什么需要我们中的一个人来救他呢?
If Ben's so magnificent, then why did he need one of us to save him?
Ben? Ben不是...
Ben? Ben is not...
简单点说
I will try to make this as simple as I can.
你们不在名单里 因为你们有瑕疵
You are not on the list because you are flawed
因为你们愤怒
Because you are angry
虚弱 恐惧
And weak and frightened.
越了解你们的人
The more I learn about your people,
我就越怀疑 你们是不是真的无所不知
the more I suspect you're not as omniscient as you'd have us believe.
别装作你很了解我们
Don't speak to us as if you know us.
我当然不了解你 Sayid Jarrah
Of course I don't know you, Sayid Jarrah.
我怎么会呢?
How could I?
Kate Austen 你对我来说就是个陌生人
And you, Kate Austen, are a complete stranger to me.
但John Locke 你...我想起来...
But you, John Locke, you, I might have a fleeting memory of,
我一定是糊涂了
but I must be confused,
因为我认识的John Locke曾是...
because the John Locke I know was para...
来看看这个
Look at this.
在这边 快点
Over here. Come on.
看来我们到了
Well, looks like we're here.
这能行吗?
Will this work?
是的 能行
Yes. Work.
能帮一下Sun的忙吗
Sun Please... Help.
好的
Ok.
真难闻啊
Smells great.
我们来处理吧
Let's get it over with.
我妈妈最怕这个了
This was my mother's worst fear.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
最后我就干这个
That I would end up doing something very much like this,
做诱饵 她对我的期望值很高
cutting bait. She had high hopes for my future.
他们也没想到我会嫁给渔夫的儿子
They did not include me marrying a fisherman's son.
看来我们都不能实现母亲的愿望了
Well, I guess we don't always turn out like our mothers want.
当然 我妈妈从来不做事
Of course, mine never worked a day in her life.
我妈妈曾是个图书管理员
My mom was a librarian.
曾是?
Was?
我们该干活了
We should get this stuff out there.
你去哪儿了?
Where were you?
回家洗了个澡
I went home to take a shower.
那一定很舒服
That must have been nice.
他们说她还在手术中
They said she was still in surgery.
我也受伤了 Lindsey姑妈
I had glass in my hair, Aunt Lindsey.
我很高兴你恢复精神了
Well, I'm glad that you're feeling refreshed.
下午好 你是她女儿吗?
Good afternoon. Are you the daughter?
我是Woodrufffrom医生 神经科的
I'm Dr. Woodruff from neurosurgery.
她还要接受几天的观察
I'll be observing your mother for the next few days.
她怎么样?
How is she?
我们设法稳定伤势
We've managed to stabilize her immediate injuries
可她头部受到了创伤
But your mother suffered a severe head trauma.
我们要等她头部的肿块消退后
We'll have to wait for the swelling in her brain to go down
才能给她做全面的检查
before we can determine the full extent of her injuries.
但恐怕她受到了大面积的伤害
But...I'm afraid we're looking at fairly widespread damage.
那是什么意思?
What does that mean?
意思是她的生命要靠这些仪器维持
It means that right now these machines are sustaining her life.
但不会一直...
But it won't always be...
当她醒来 她不会...
I mean, when she wakes up, she won't...
我不能很肯定的告诉你
I can't say with any real confidence
她会醒过来
that she will wake up.
她能听见我们吗?
Can she hear us?
我希望是这样
I like to think she can.
她这样要多久?
How long will she be like this?
也许一天 一个星期或是一年
Could be a day, a week or years.
我们只能等待
We'll just have to wait and see.
但我能保证你们她会受到很好的照顾的
But I can assure you, she'll be well looked after.
那很好 只是我们付不起那么多
Oh, that's very nice, but we can't pay for that.
别担心 有人已经帮你们解决了
Don't worry. Her expenses have already been taken care of.
是谁?
By whom?
他让我保密
I've been asked to keep that confidential.
1... 2...
One... Two...
不!
No!
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉 伙计
I'm sorry, man.
我很抱歉
I said I'm sorry.
你到底想干什么?
What the hell is wrong with you?
我在打一只野猪 我不知道你们在这里
I was shooting at a boar. I had no idea you were out here.
Charlie在哪里?
Where's Charlie?
他在营地里
He's back at the camp.
我很抱歉吓到了你们...
I'm really sorry if I frightened...
所以就你一个人?
So it's just you?
你就正好出现在我们设陷阱的地方?
Hunting, in the exact same spot as we're setting our trap?
我在追一头野猪 Claire
I was following a boar, Claire.
那可真是巧啊
So it's just a coincidence, then.
那头猪呢?
Where is it?
它跑了
It got away.
你不想让我捉住那只鸟是吗?
You don't want me to catch the birds, do you?
你和Charlie 到底怎么了?
You and Charlie..what's going on?
我为什么不想你捉住它?
Why wouldn't I want you to catch the birds?
这是什么?
What is it?
别碰它!
Don't touch it!
别靠近它
Don't even get near it.
这些高压电线架是什么?
What are these pylons?
你认为呢?
What do you think they are?
一种区域防御系统
A security perimeter.
任何人走进去时
Those sensors on the side would be triggered
就会触发陷阱
if anyone passed between them.
这是警报系统或是陷阱
It's an alarm system or a trap.
我们在这里会很安全
Either way, we'll be safer going around it.
你是对的 这是个防御系统
You are right. It was a security perimeter,
但经过这么多年想必这些都已经失效了
but like everything else on this island, it hasn't functioned in years.
别耍我们了
Of course it hasn't.
如果你想浪费时间 随便你
If you wish to waste your time, be my guest.
电线架围绕着整个营地
The pylons encircle the entire barracks.
你们这样是进不去的
There is no going around them.
如果你不相信我的话 看看你的地图
If you don't believe me, look at your map.
看来他说的是真的
He appears to be telling the truth.
John? John!
谢谢你
Thank you.
我的上帝
Oh, my god.
抱歉
Sorry.
看上去像大脑出血
Looks like he suffered a cerebral hemorrhage.
你为什么要这样做?我们需要他!
Why did you do that? We needed him!
他们不会拿他交换Jack的
They were never gonna trade him for Jack.
-你不知道的  -那你也不知道
-You don't know that.  -You don't know it, either.
我们知道的是 他射杀了他的同伴
What we do know is that he shot one of his own people who didn't want to be in this exact situation,
所以我坚持我的想法
so I'm gonna stick with my opinion.
我们至少能讨论一下
We could have discussed it.
我们本来就不该带上他
Nobody asked me about it when we brought him along in the 1st place.
行了
All right.
抱歉我不知道他们有某种电磁武器系统
Pardon me for not knowing that they had a sonic weapon fence.
我不知道他会死
I didn't know he was gonna die. How would I know that?
你来的目的是什么?
Why are you really here?
是为了Jack吗?
Are you here for Jack?
那还有什么原因?
Why else would I be here?
这事我们稍后再解决
We'll talk about this later.
我同意
Fine by me.
那我们怎么穿过去?
Just tell me how we're gonna go through this.
我们另找办法
We're not gonna go through it.
我们翻过去
We're going over it.
Sayid, 斧头放在哪了?
Sayid, where's the axe?
在他的背包里
It's in his pack.
等等 我来拿
No, wait a minute. I got it.
我来吧
Here, I got it.
我认为你原来不知道有C-4的
I thought you didn't know there was any c-4.
好吧 我承认
Well, I stand corrected.
你为什么带上它?
Why did you take it?
你永远不知道小小的C-4也许能派上用处
You never know when a little c-4 might come in handy.
你必须做的更好
You'll have to do better than that.
好了好了
Okay, there you go.
你到底怎么了 Charlie?
What's going on with you, Charlie?
我只是把Aaron放下
I just put Aaron down
不 你和Desmond 怎么了?
No, you and Desmond, what's going on?
我不知道你在说什么
What you're talking about.
那你不知道Desmond开枪吓跑了我们要捉的鸟吗?
So you don't know anything about Desmond shooting off
his gun and scaring away the birds?
我早上一直和Aaron在一起
I've been with Aaron all morning.
你在撒谎 Charlie
You're lying to me, Charlie.
我没有
I am not lying.
那个早上醒来
What happened to the guy who woke up this morning
准备野餐的家伙到底怎么了?
who wanted to go and have a picnic and seize the day?
你真的想知道?
You really want to know the truth?
那闪光会是任何东西
That glint you saw could have been anything
粘在鸟爪子上的玻璃残渣
a piece of glass stuck in the bird's foot...
或许什么都没有
or it could have been nothing at all.
我不想让你有错误的希望 Claire
I don't want to advocate false hope, Claire, that's all.
很抱歉 我想到这个主意
Well, I'm sorry. I bothered you with my stupid ideas,
这永远都不会再发生了
and, it won't ever happen again.
Charlie 我不想我的孩子围绕在谎言之中
And, Charlie, I don't want my baby around lies.
你是反应过度了
I think you might be overreacting.
反应过度?
Overreacting?
不 我以为我能和你在一起 我能依赖你
No, I thought you were here for me, that I could count on you.
但我错了
I was wrong.
不 Claire
No, Claire!
我还是靠我自己吧 至少现在我意识到了
I'm on my own, and at least I know that now.
Claire
走吧!
Just go!
早上好 亲爱的
Morning, dear.
我喜欢你新的医生
Oh, I like your new doctor.
新的医生?
What new doctor?
是个美国人
Oh, the American.
现在和你母亲在一起
He's in with your mum now.
不好意思
Excuse me.
护士说
The nurse said
你是医生?
Are you a doctor?
是的
Yes
我很抱歉
I'm very sorry.
打扰你们
I shouldn't be disturbing you.
我该走了
I was just leaving.
你在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我才要走 Lindsey
I was just on my way out, Lindsey.
如果Carole知道你在这里...
If Carole knew you were here...
怎么? 她会做什么?
She'd what? What would she do?
她不会表现的像你那样
She wouldn't be acting the way you are.
Lindsey姨妈 到底怎么回事?
Aunt Lindsey, what's going on here?
他是谁?
Who is he?
这不重要 你走吧
It doesn't matter. Just go.
或许你应该告诉她 Lindsey
Maybe you should tell her, Lindsey.
求你就别管我们了
Please, just leave us alone.
-你没有资格来决定这些  -不
-You are not the arbiter here.  -No.
-在这种情况下  -你是趁我姐姐受伤的机会
-In these circumstances  -You are taking advantage of my sister's situation
我不认为Claire有权知道...
I believe Claire has every right to know...
大家冷静一下!
just stop it!
是你付的医疗费?
Are you the one paying the bills?
是你照料这些事的?
Are you the one taking care of all this?
是的
Yes.
那你是谁?
Then who are you?
我是你的父亲 Claire
I'm your father, Claire.
如果有东西切断了系统的水平面
The system appears to fire a sonic pulse
那就会触发电磁回路
when an object breaks the plane between two pylons.
所以
So...
只要我们不去碰那个水平面 我们就会没事的
as long as we don't break the plane, we should remain unharmed.
为什么不用炸药呢?
Why not just use the plastic explosive you took?
你想死就随便你
Be my guest. You wanna go stick it on there?
谁爬过去后 给一个安全信号
Whoever climbs over, give those sensors a wide berth.
我先来
I'll go first.
帮我一把
Give me a hand.
我想我是第二个
I guess I'll go next.
行了
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
不要为那事烦心了
You have every right to be upset.
这一点都没道理
It just doesn't make any sense.
Desmond从没打过野猪
Desmond's never gone boar hunting before,
而野猪也不会那么靠近海滩
and the boar never come that close to the beach.
不管发生了什么
Well, whatever is going on,
他们还在那边说话呢
they're still talking about it.
你能看一下他吗?
Can you watch him?
你要去干什么?
What are you going to do?
找出答案
Get some answers.
一会儿就来
I'll be with you in a sec.
行了
There you go.
10块钱
It'll be 10 bucks.
你来这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
请你喝杯咖啡?
Buy you a cup of coffee?
我和你没什么好说的
I have nothing to say to you.
Claire今晚我就离开 从此我会从你的生活中消失的
I'm leaving tonight, then I'll be out of your life forever.
就一杯咖啡
Just one cup of coffee.
这都是真的
So it's true.
是的
Yes, it's true.
你是怎么知道发生事故了?
How'd you find out about the accident?
一个在悉尼的朋友告诉我的
A doctor friend here in Sydney told me.
你母亲一进手术室我就接到了电话
I got the call the minute your mother went into surgery.
为什么她告诉我你死了?
Why did she tell me that you're dead?
是因为我和她在一起留下了许多美好的时光吧
Well, because I..no doubt...left her with so many wonderful memories.
我们有段美妙的时光
Look, we had a fling.
我回络杉矶后她才告诉我她怀孕了
I was back in Los Angeles when she told me that she was pregnant,
她将有个还孩子 你
that she was going to have the baby...have you.
你不想见我?
You didn't want to see me?
不 在你小的时候我来看过你几次
No. I came out a bunch of times when you were little.
我过来买玩具给你
I stayed over,gave you toys.
给你唱歌
I sang to you.
为什么你后来不来了呢?
Why'd you stop coming?
因为你的姨妈恨我
'cause your aunt hates me,
而你母亲不愿意接受
and your mother didn't like the fact that...
我有另外一个家庭的现实
I had another family.
那你现在来做什么?
Why are you here now, then? Why'd you come?
就为了给我们付医疗费?
You could've just paid her bills from the states.
我来是想帮助你们
I came over because I wanted to help.
帮助什么?
Help with what?
Claire 你母亲还活着
Your mother is alive...
但基本上是个植物人
but she's not really living.
你到底什么意思?
What that's supposed to mean?
意思是是时候选择
It means that now may be the time
其它的道路来减轻她的痛苦
to look at other alternatives, other ways to relieve her pain.
撤掉她身上的仪器是非法的
Now it is illegal to turn off her machines,
但我知道一种合法的办法
but I know of ways that can achieve the same effect without the legal consequences.
闭嘴!
Just stop it!
你不是来帮我的
You didn't come here to help me.
你是来弥补自己的过失的
You came here to try and fix a mistake that you made.
不 亲爱的 不是这样的
No, honey, that's not true.
你以为付了医疗费就能让你变成一个高尚的人吗?
You think that just paying her bills makes you noble or something?
你来这里是想杀死她?
You come down here, and you try and get me to kill her?
你走吧
You know, just go.
为什么你不走呢?
Why don't you just go?
回到你真实的家庭去
Go back to your real family.
你知道
You know
你也许是我的父亲
You might be my father
但我甚至都不知道你的名字
But I don't even know your name...
而我也不想知道
And I, um, I want it to stay that way.
Claire...Claire
Claire听我说
Listen to me.
听我说
别让你母亲以错误的原因活下去
Do not keep your mother alive for the wrong reasons.
希望还是罪责 相信我
Now there is hope and there is guilt, and believe me,
我知道这的区别
I know the difference.
再见了 孩子
Good-bye, kiddo.
很高兴再次见到你
It's great seeing you again.
你到底在做什么?
What the hell are you doing?
你跟踪我
You followed me.
退后!
Stay back!
这有只鸟
It's one of the birds.
退后!
Stay back!
你怎么知道会在这里的?
How did you know it was gonna be here?
我不知道
I didn't.
是的 你知道
Yes, you did.
你一定知道
You had to.
这就是你和Charlie争执的事情
That's what you and Charlie were arguing about.
你知道的
You knew.
我怎么会知道?
How would I?
你不去任何地方找
I don't know, but you know,you walked straight here
就径直来到这里
no doubt at all about where you were going.
在这片海滩这块石头
You came right to this beach and right to this rock,
而且很巧的是 这有只鸟
and low and behold, there's the bird.
到底发生了什么 Desmond?
What t hell is going on, Desmond?
看见那块地方了吗?
See that spot over there?
那就是Charlie滑倒的地方
That's where Charlie slipped and fell in.
他撞在石头上
He got pounded again and again by the rocks and
摔断了他的脖子
broke his neck.
什么?
What?
你在说什么?
What...what are you talking about?
那就是Charlie死的地方
That's where Charlie died.
看Desmond找到了什么
Look what Desmond found.
太好了
How about that?
真的有标签啊
It does have a tag.
你是对的
You were right.
Desmond把一切都告诉我了
Desmond told me everything
那些幻觉
about all his visions
他知道你会被电击
That he knew you were gonna get hit by lightning,
为了救我你会淹死
that you were gonna drown trying to rescue me in the ocean
为了捉这只鸟 你摔死了
how you died trying to get me this bird.
你不会相信的 是吧?
You don't believe all that, do you?
谁把电视关了?
Now who turned the telly off?
他们不知道我妈妈喜欢看自然节目吗?
Don't they know how much you love your nature shows?
这样好多了
That's better.
妈妈 你今天怎么样?
So how are you today, mum?
睡的好吗?
Did you have an okay night?
我...
Listen...
要告诉你一些事
Something I have to tell you,
一些我很早就应该告诉你的事
something I should have told you a long time ago.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
我要把他送走
I'm giving it away.
这样做最好
It's for the best.
最好是这样
I wish...
我不知道你怎么...
I don't know how you did it...
独自把我抚养大的
raising me alone.
一定很艰难
That must have been so hard,
而我真是...
and I was just...
一团糟
awful...
糟透了
让你操心了
So horrible to you.
对不起 妈妈
I'm so sorry, mum.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry
为了我在车里对你说的不好的话
So sorry for all the awful things I said to you in the car
说我恨你
That...I hated you...
说我不希望你是我的母亲
and that I wished you weren't my mother
说我希望你死
and that I wished you were dead.
都是我的错
It's all my fault
那场事故 所有一切
the accident, everything.
我很抱歉 妈妈
I'm so sorry, mom.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
我会回来看你的 好吗?
I'll see you soon, okay?
我们是815航班的幸存者
To whom it may concern,we are survivors of Oceanic flight 815.
我们已经在岛上待了80天了
We have survived on this island for 80 days.
起飞后6小时
We were six hours into the flight when the pilot said we were off course
我们的飞机转向Fiji
and turned back towards Fiji.
接着撞毁在这座岛上
We hit turbulence and crashed.
我们一直在这里等待救援
We've been waiting here all this time
可就是没人来
waiting for rescue that has not come.
我们不知道我们在哪儿
We do not know where we are.
只知道你们找不到我们
We only know you have not found us.
我们尽力在岛上生存下来
We've done our best to live on this island.
有些人已经接受了没人救援的现实
Some of us have come to accept we may never leave it.
飞机遇难后不是每个人都活了下来
Not all of us have survived since the crash,
但也有新生命的诞生
but there is new life, too,
这给了我们希望
and with it, there is hope.
我们还活着
We are alive.
请不要放弃我们
Please don't give up on us.
这...
It's...
真是完美Claire
It's perfect, Claire.
我也不会放弃你的 Charlie
You know, I'm not giving up on you either, Charlie.
一切都会好起来的
It's gonna be okay.
你也会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
我们一起度过
We'll get through this together.
怎么了?
What?
我们到了
We're here.
===================================
本字幕由YYeTs美剧翻译组制作
YYeTs美剧首发网站www.YYETS.com
===================================